World where I grew up,
how wondrous and beautiful you are!
Everything is in my hands
while I walk,
while I am full of strength.
To live in the joy of days,
to burn brightly,
but not become ash.
World where I grew up,
look proudly at who I have become.
The very, very brightest feeling
You are like art
You are a bright light
The very, very brightest feeling
You are like art
You are a bright light
Maybe, someday on this planet,
in the greatest, greatest trouble,
In the most derelict, crumbling cottage,
those next to me won’t be the same.
And I will remember the home
where I grew up.
I will remember everything
so familiar it brings tears:
The river, the greenhouse,
and your laughter behind the wall,
Quiet comfort, deep peace.
The very, very brightest feeling
You are like art
You are a bright light
The very, very brightest feeling
You are like art
You are a bright light
The very, very brightest feeling
You are like art
You are a bright light